guys I went to the worst escape room
ever
it's called Ikea
someone missing in your life there there
I always get lost at Ikea I found a
security card I'm like dude can you help
me get out of here
he's like bro I've been lost here since
Halloween
this is a costume
I see dead people
I have an addiction that's ruining my
life I feel like I can be honest okay
it's hard for me to talk about
it's called Costco
Costco is the only place you try to save
money by spending everything that you
have
my friends brag to me about shopping at
Costco they're like man come here check
this out check this out
I save so much money
I lost my house
I'm sleeping on toilet paper
I need help
that's why they pack your stuff in
cardboard boxes before you leave they
know you're going to be homeless
there's certain things that don't make
sense at Costco they have all those
clothes for sale but no Jurassic room to
try them on
so I'm in the frozen food section taken
off my pants
just don't need a bite
you to buy ketchup I'm giving it out for
Halloween
there's one reason I love Costco and I
want you guys to clap if you're on board
it's those food samples do you guys
agree yes
yes
you guys are my kind of crowd I love
those samples that's why I take all my
first dates
since I never normally ask I'm like oh
are these organic
my cart is filled with beef jerky and
cigarettes
that is all I'm buying
and anytime I eat one of those free
samples I always act overly excited like
I'm trying not to hurt their feelings
because my reaction is so ridiculous I
sound like an idiot I put one in my
mouth I'm like wow
this is amazing what do you call it
Dorito
it's a good Dorito
foreign
there's one place I wish they had free
samples that they don't the pharmacy
[Laughter]
that would be awesome because you don't
know what you're gonna get
my reaction would also be ridiculous I
put one in my mouth I'm like wow this is
amazing what do you call it
birth control
can I get another one
that's where my neighbor he's sleeping
on toilet paper